[Music]
Microsoft has just announced a series of
new autonomous agents are you ready to
meet your new crew let's jump in
together and explore the sales order
agent the business at the heart of this
demo is Kronos Furniture it's a really
busy time of year and the owner of
Cronos will be relieved to reduce the
strain on a sellers using the new sales
order agent that's quickly said set it
up this is very simple I'm in business
Central and if we go ahead and click on
the sales order icon this is where I set
the agent up first I want to go in and
add the shared email address that
customers send requests
to I add these details in
here and when I'm ready click next
clicking finish the next thing I can do
is go ahead and choose which users have
access to the agent if I click on manage
user access
it's really easy to go ahead and add
those individual users in just like that
they have access to the ability to
review and approve agent actions I go
ahead and activate it and it's ready to
go no additional configuration needed
that was quick are you ready to see it
in action let's head over to Outlook
here we can see that I'm in the mailbox
of one of our customers Ian Ian is an
office manager for a company that is
opening up a new branch and he needs to
order all of the office furniture and
supplies to get started on Ian's behalf
let's send an email to cronis asking
about options for conference tables
chairs and paint in this email we can
also see I've gone ahead and added a
specific deadline for when the items
need to be delivered by along with the
purchase order number which is actually
an external number used in Ian's own Erp
system this could be referenced which
will make it easier for him I can go
ahead and click Send and the agent will
have immediate access to the email if
Ian has sent an email with a clear ask
for quote for specific items the agent
could go ahead and immediately do that
in this case we send some questions and
so the agent can actually engage with
the in back and forward to answer them
we're back in Mrs Central and in a
second the agent will go ahead and pick
up the email when we think about this at
scale my team can work with the agent
however they would like they can reserve
a few times per day to check the agent
and approve requests several at a time
or they can check it more frequently and
approve it as new replies are generated
by the agent either way their time is
freed up to focus on other more pressing
sales
tasks we can see here that the agent has
gone ahead and mapped the email to Ian's
account and has actually created a draft
email if we click in we can see the full
email let's click on
review and now we can see here the email
that the agent has generated it has a
full list of all of the conference
tables chairs and white paint that Crona
sells I feel good about this email so I
can go ahead and approve it and it will
get sent straight to Ian let's click on
confirm and it will
go back in Ian's inbox we're able to go
ahead and confirm his final requirements
and ask for a quote if his reply is
vague the agent would reply to clarify
his exact details but in this case we're
giving a really clear
response we want to go ahead and order
two conference
tables eight of the London chairs and
two cans of the eggshell white
paint with all the information that it
needs the agent will be able to create a
quote let's head back into business
Central normally creating a quote would
take several minutes for each individual
customer times up by the number of
requests that they get each day and
honestly there just isn't enough time to
make sure the team is still kept in the
loop someone will be able to see that
quote and approve it before it gets sent
out here we go here's the sales quote if
I go ahead and click in we can see all
of the rich details that it's
captured I love this attention to detail
it's picked up the products that he
chose mapped them to the skew numbers
and pulled in lots of information about
price sales tax and so on it's also
noticed that Ian shared a few other
details there we can see the delivery
date and there's that purchase order
number that's all been incorporated into
the quote all I need to do is Click
review to see the email that has that
quote
attached when I'm happy with it I click
confirm and that quote will get sent
straight over to
Ian if we go ahead and jump back into
Outlook
there we can see the quote Ian has
received in PDF format with all the
information that he needs to feel
confident moving forward with the sales
deal jumping back into business Central
one of my favorite things is how clearly
each step of each customer engagement is
captured in business
Central this allows all of the business
Central users working with the agent to
stay in the loop and easily get involved
whenever they're
needed heading into a busy period any
business would be relieved that they set
up the agent the sales order agent is a
team agent helping reduce order
processing time meaning customers get an
improved experience and faster delivery
even during busy periods
[Music]